[{"answer": "He", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "*You'r", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I don't remember", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Maybe I was kissing someone and he bit me", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Can't a boy be a Dorrit", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You do it then", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend's practically the youngest of us. She should be the", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "They take the babies so they won't ever have to tell them that they were orphans", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I was dreaming about you. How beautiful you were", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I was", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Then I wasn't beautiful", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It was just the ether, my friend..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " They want to replace me! The that place wants to", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Some new", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Cirrhosi", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "*Alcoho", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "*Alcoho", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Barely. It hardly mattered that I knew him", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I'm happy I amuse you", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Try to look at it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Are you really so", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I don't need your gratitude", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " my friend thinks apples are boring", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You said,", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes, so what. It's nothing serious, really. Just a small defect", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "He is a goddamn psychiatris", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "One has to be more than", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "How could you not", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " That's what", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Just tell me. Do you want me to go? Do you want me to stay", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "*Wha", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I grew up with my friend. I began my adult life with him", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No! That's not all there is to it! I love you, to", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Fine. That's all there is to it then", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Okay, oka", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You okay, my friend", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I don't like watching anyone be sick", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You're not yet three months, are you", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I know more than I want to know about it. Who's the father", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No. Nothing is nothing. I want my friend to come home. I'm afraid to see him, too", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Tell that my friend to mind his own business, Muddy", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Tell him what you want, Mudd", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "my friend has runned away", "docId": "Cider-House-Rules_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "She took off on the bicycle, man", "qsentId": 46}]